tuzara.com 2008-05-31

# Tuzara.com :: Privacy Policy

Effective as of May 15, 2003  

Important!  
[ Click Here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/alerts/privtipsalrt.htm) For important information about safe browsing on the Internet

Tuzara takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to personalize your experience at our website. This privacy statement explains how we gather information and how we protect your privacy. The Tuzara Interactive Social Exchange is a private adult (18 and over) interactive entertainment community that enables its members to interact via integrated media and live events. Tuzara was founded to create an interactive network of interesting and active young professionals who enjoy socializing at live events and for whom the Internet is their primary entertainment, media and information resource. Tuzara, LLC ("TUZARA") believes that communities can only truly be built through interaction and participation among members based on trust, privacy and freedom of expression. In order to do this, we must ask for certain personal information. 

We make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.   
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Tuzara does not own or control, or to people that Tuzara does not employ or manage. 

**Except where you are expressly informed otherwise or as described immediately below, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information except to the financial institution that processes your credit card or check transaction unless required by law or for the protection of your membership.

The Information We Gather

**  
To accomplish our goal of creating an interactive entertainment and networking community, we must gather personal information, which may or may not include: customer-specified Tuzara..com username, gender, age, ethnic background, appearance, religion, income range, occupation, preference/lifestyle information and general geographic location. Much of this information is optional, and meant to be seen by members and visitors to the site but cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, etc. Some information is gathered from members and guests who apply for the various services our site offers. This information includes, but is not limited to: email address, first name, last name, birth date, credit card number or checking account information for payment, a user-specified password, mailing address, Zip Code/Postal Code and telephone number. 

**Ordering Online.** When you order, we need to know your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. 

**Promotions, Online Surveys & Announcements.** If you decide to participate in an online survey, subscribe to an email list, enter a contest or use one of our other promotional features, we may ask for your name, address, email address and other pertinent information to administer the contest, tabulate survey results or add you to subscriber lists. Contact and other information collected for contests will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.

**Browsing.** We may use "cookies" to help us process your order and to customize information that we may present to you. A cookie is a small text file that does not personally identify users, although it does identify a user's computer. Cookies do not pose a threat to your computer, and they do not contain viruses. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change this feature in your browser. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user rejects a cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas on our site. We occasionally use cookies to anonymously track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site or for advertising tracking purposes. In addition, cookies may be used on our site to allow enhanced capabilities such as chat. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Some information supplied by the user is intended to be viewed by visitors (e.g. information contained in public profiles, public and private Showcases, etc.) to the site. This information cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, etc.

**Tuzara.com Affiliate Partners.** The Affiliate Partner program is a vehicle for other activity, entertainment and lifestyle sites, organizations and professionals to link to the Tuzara.com site. Information submitted by the Affiliate Partner is used for establishing and maintaining a business relationship. No personal or business information is shared outside the relationship between Tuzara..com and the Affiliate Partner. Affiliate Partners may not view or access private information on Tuzara.com subscribers.

**Aggregate.** This is information we collect that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users to the site.   
Communicating with Tuzara. We primarily use Email addresses submitted by members to verify enrollment and when forwarding event announcements and responses to personal advertisements. Respondees' email addresses are not disclosed to the responder. We may also use a user's email address to send news regarding our site, but the user may choose not to receive email of this type by emailing [support@tuzara.com](mailto:support@tuzara.com) . Email addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law or to protect members of Tuzara.com. All private information can be updated or deleted by the user at any time. 

**Links.** This site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that Tuzara..com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information.** Tuzara.com gives users several options for modifying or removing their information from our database please visit your "My Tuzara" page or email [ support@tuzara.com](mailto:support@tuzara.com) . 

**Security.** Tuzara.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order process asks users to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please email [support@tuzara.com](mailto:support@tuzara.com) . 

**Email Choice/Opt-out.** Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners or affiliates may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the email. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure.  **  
Tuzara does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Tuzara under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Tuzara communicate with you about offers from Tuzara and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Tuzara's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

**Prospective Member Information.** Tuzara.com also collects prospect information from our users. Our users may provide another person's information, such as their friend's e-mail address, in order to send them content or offerings from Tuzara.com.. The prospect's information is used for the purpose for which it was submitted. Prospective members may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

**Your Consent.** By using Tuzara.com, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your personal and non-personal information as described above. You also authorize the export of personal information and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of California and the USA, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the USA in the State of California. 

Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on forums, through email, or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others. Always be smart about the information you provide online.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.** We may amend our Privacy Policy, but if we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you can always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Any changes will only apply to information collected after the change is posted.

Tuzara, LLC.  
Customer Care  
6114 La Salle Ave., Suite 404  
Oakland, CA 94611  
(866) 488-9272  
[support@tuzara.com](mailto:support@tuzara.com)  Copyright © 2003 by Tuzara.com  
All rights reserved. Do not duplicate or redistribute in any form.
